<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RSS Feeds</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sports1">SINGAPORE: Indian shuttler B Sai Praneeth dished out a dominating performance to outclass Korea\’s Lee Dong-keun in straight games and reach his maiden Super Series final at the Singapore Open here on Saturday.
Praneeth, who had reached the finals at Syed Modi Grand Prix Gold in January only to suffer an injury in his shoulders, continued his rampaging run in the tournament to thrash three-time Korea Masters Grand Prix Gold winner Lee 21 -6, 21-8 in a lop-sided semifinal match.

The 24-year-old from Hyderabad, who had clinched the Canada Open last year, came out with a well sorted strategy and executed it brilliantly to completely blow away his opponent in the opening game.

In the second game, Praneeth continued to dominate the proceedings and zoomed to a 9-1 lead. The Korean managed to reduce the deficit to 4-10 before the Indian entered the break with a 11-4 lead.

</string>
    <string name="sports2">Borussia Dortmund considered withdrawing from the Champions League following the bomb attack on the team bus, according to CEO Hans-Joachim Watzke.
Three devices exploded close to the vehicle as it made its way to Signal Iduna Park for the quarter-final first leg with Monaco on Tuesday.
Defender Marc Bartra suffered a broken wrist and the match was rescheduled for Wednesday, with Monaco going on to win 3-2.
Players including Nuri Sahin and Roman Burki, who was sitting next to Bartra when the explosions took place, admitted afterwards that focusing on the match had been extremely difficult.
Watzke has promised that Dortmund\’s squad will be offered counselling if they wish, adding: "The players have the opportunity to deal with the psychological side of the attack with experts and to get any help from us."

</string>


<string name="sports3">Five-time Grand Slam champion Maria Sharapova has criticised the International Tennis Federation (ITF) for not doing enough to make her aware that meldonium had been added to the list of banned substances last year.
Sharapova\’s initial two-year suspension was reduced to 15 months after she tested positive at the 2016 Australian Open for meldonium, a medication the Russian had been taking within the rules but which was then reclassified as a banned drug.
Sharapova did, however, say that she had become "complacent" and was responsible for failing the drug test.

"Ultimately the fault was mine," she added. "I had been getting clearance on everything I was taking for seven years and I became complacent."

</string>

<string name="tech1">BEIJING: A Chinese-made self-driving truck has passed a navigation test, heralding a new era of intelligent, automated heavy vehicles, official media reported today.

FAW Jiefang, the leading truck manufacturer, debuted the self-driving truck at FAW Tech Center in Changchun city, Jilin province.

The truck, which FAW Jiefang plans to commercialize as early as next year, was able to recognize obstacles, slow down, make a detour and speed up, state-run Xinhua news agency reported.
The intelligent driving vehicle reacted correctly to traffic lights, adaptive cruise control, remote commands and successfully overtook, the report said.
The technology may prove more practical when it is used on trucks than private cars as truck drivers are more likely to drive tired, the report added.

</string>

<string name="tech2">BENGALURU: Digital wallet player Paytm has partnered with luxury brand distributor Genesis Luxury in India which markets and distributes global luxury and premium brands in the country.

This would allow users to scan the store QR code and pay using the balance on their Paytm wallet. "The essence of Genesis Luxury is in our philosophy that luxury brands are an experience above everything else.
Our great mix of designer labels from across the globe combined with a superlative payment experience using Paytm would help us to treat our customers with the most state-of the art retail experience ever," said Sanjay Kapoor, managing director at Genesis Luxury.

Tying up with offline retail stores in the premium segment will help Paytm increase the transaction value and benefit from high ticket purchases by their users.

</string>

<string name="tech3">SAN FRANCISCO: Alphabet\’s life sciences unit Verily has unveiled a wrist-worn "Study Watch" designed to gather complex health data in clinical studies.

Study Watch is meant for research and will be put to work in several studies including a multi-year study to identify patterns in the progression of Parkinson\’s disease, according to a blog post by Verily team members David He, Tushar Parlikar, and Harry Xiao.

"The ability to passively capture health data is critical to the success of continuous care platforms and clinical research," the post from the Google sister company said.

"Study Watch represents another step in our targeted efforts to create new tools for unobtrusive bio-sensing."

Study Watch appeared styled after a traditional wrist-worn timepiece, and boasted features including long battery life and encryption for stored data.

</string>

<string name="pol1">KOCHI: NCP chief Sharad Pawar today lashed out at the Congress for "failing" to form a government in Goa, saying his party MLA voted for the BJP in the trust vote as "action" was missing from the Congress leadership to form a government there.

He said it was possible for the Congress, which emerged as the single largest party with 16 seats in the Goa Assembly, to form the government and get a majority with support of the NCP and other regional political parties.

Pawar said NCP MLA Churchill Alemao supported the BJP to form the government to avoid "re-election" to the state assembly.

The MLA waited for three days when the question came for voting to form the government. The NCP was eager to support the Congress and it\’s expectation was that party should form the government, he said.

</string>

<string name="pol2">Security personnel allegedly shot dead a 22-year-old in Srinagar on Saturday, triggering fresh protests in a valley tense over several video clips showing alleged human rights violation by the armed forces.
A police spokesperson said they were trying to ascertain the cause and circumstance leading to the death of Sajad Hussain Sheikh of Chandoosa in Baramulla. Sheikh was based at SD Colony in Batamaloo, on the outskirts of Srinagar.
“Somebody shot somebody. We are verifying,” said Imtiyaz Parray, the Srinagar superindent of police Srinagar.
The state\’s director general of police SP Vaid said there are allegations that the youth died in firing by Border Security Force (BSF) jawans.
He said some BSF vehicles travelling in the area lost their way to the airport when a group of people pelted stones on the convoy. The BSF personnel allegedly opened fire in retaliation leading to the death. “I spoke to SSP Srinagar, he told me that they were trying to ascertain,” Vaid said.
</string>

<string name="pol3">MUMBAI: In a major embarrassment for chief minister Devendra Fadnavis, BJP leader and former minister Eknath Khadse on Saturday hosted the opposition leaders who were taking out a Sangharsha Yatra to press for a complete loan waiver for the farmers.
Khadse confirmed that a section of opposition leaders, comprising NCP leaders Ajit Pawar and Jayant Patil and leader of the opposition Radhakrishna Vikhe Patil, visited his house in Jalgaon district on Saturday. "Since my house is located on the highway, they expressed a desire to have tea with me. It was a courtesy visit and I hosted tea for them... there is no politics in it," Khadse said.

The visit caused a flutter particularly because Khadse is at a logger heads with Fadnavis ever since a judicial probe was ordered into his MIDC land deal in June 2016. The committee has still not completed the inquiry even after four extensions. Khadse was expecting that the probe to be completed in three months and that he would be re-inducted into the cabinet immediately. However, that appears to be a distant dream now.

</string>

<string name="ent1">After the Central Board of Film Certification (CBFC) demanded that \’Noor\’ makers edit a reference to veteran journalist Barkha Dutt in the film, its leading lady Sonakshi Sinha says the censor body needs to have a uniform approach towards movies.
In \’Noor\’, Sonakshi plays a journalist who idolises Barkha Dutt, but the CBFC has asked the makers to edit the surname Dutt.

When asked about it, Sonakshi said "The censor board really needs to come to a consensus within themselves on what is right in one film... Is not right in another film.”
"There is no consistency in what they censor or what they don\’t censor, so I think they first need to come to a consensus."
</string>

<string name="ent2">Hrithik Roshan\’s turn as a dubbing artist in his last release, the Sanjay Gupta-directed \’Kaabil\’, had sparked off requests from real-life professionals for a meet-and-greet with the actor. On Friday, 14 of Bollywood\’s leading dubbing artists met with the 43-year-old actor at his Juhu residence. They exchanged notes over tea, coffee and sandwiches. "Hrithik played his practice recordings from when he was prepping for \’Kaabil\’ all by himself. It was really sweet of him to do that. He is a warm person and there is so much that we got to learn from him," says dubbing artist Nishka Raheja.
Hrithik was inquisitive about how they work, while the dubbing artists marveled at his in-depth research for the role and felt a sense of pride in the way he had portrayed the role and made it stand out in the film. The group could also relate to a scene in which Hrithik\’s character is required to can a laughing dub when he is emotionally low and wants to cry.
</string>

<string name="ent3">Singer Kailash Kher, who shot to fame with the 2003 hit number \’Allah ke bande\’, has today been conferred India\’s fourth highest civilian award, the Padma Shri. He has received the recognition by President Pranab Mukherjee for his contribution to music in the country.
Earlier, while speaking to on this achievement, the 43-year-old, with a sense of pride, said that words will fall short, if he is asked about the award\’s importance for him. "Receiving such a prestigious award holds loads of importance in one\’s life; words will fall short if I try to explain it. In my case, it is even more special; it is historic. It is such an incident, which will be mentioned in books, in future."

The singer, who hails from Meerut, gave up education decades ago to pursue his dream to be a singer. Known for adding Sufi touch to songs, Kailash has crooned tracks like \’Teri deewani\’, \’Ya rabba,\’ \’Yun hi chala chal rahi\’ and many more.

</string>

    <string-array name="news_array">
        <item>@string/sports1</item>
        <item>@string/ent1</item>
        <item>@string/tech1</item>
        <item>@string/pol1</item>
        <item>@string/sports2</item>
        <item>@string/pol2</item>
        <item>@string/tech2</item>
        <item>@string/ent2</item>
        <item>@string/pol3</item>
        <item>@string/sports3</item>
        <item>@string/ent3</item>
        <item>@string/tech3</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
